How you feeling?
>> I feel good, man. I I like it's it's
it's we're excited. We are excited. Um
>> like that,
>> huh?
>> Yeah, it's cool, man. But uh no um one
we in the second round we were able to
trade back and got the same player we
would have taken had we just stayed and
picked the 55 picked up two picks uh
which is exciting and then uh and then
in the third round another opportunity
to to pick up more picks and we're
looking at the board and we just see a
lot of guys up there that we still like
that our scouts like that our coaches
like and you know gives you more ammo
So, more trade maneuvering, you know,
things to get creative with. So, it's
it's fun. Um, we haven't had a chance to
do this in two years, so add picks like
that. So, the scouts are excited. Uh,
talking, you know, coaches, they're
fired up. We'll get together up there
and start really identifying our targets
and and, uh, get them stacked and and
have a lot of fun tomorrow. But, uh,
terms of, you know, talk about Jake, uh,
just excited excited to get him. Um, a
player that unanimously, scouts,
coaches, uh, everyone had pretty much
the same exact grade on, which was a
high high-end grade. And, um, you know,
we got some calls and texts after we
took him from other teams, which always
makes you feel good, you know, damn, you
took our guy. So, it was it was fun to
hear that. But uh but he's a player that
we he's smart, tough, athletic,
intelligent, three-year starter,
durable,
um and uh player. I know the question,
you know, and is is he's a center. We
we've had long discussions in the
process. Do we feel like he could play
guard in this scheme? And the the
question the answer to that question is
absolutely.
>> So,
Chris
Yeah, I think it did a great job. Um, I
mean, home run, um, pick of Jake
Slaughter, uh, you know, like Joe said,
uh, we had him on our board. I mean,
much higher. Um, and, you know, to now
have two more players, uh, and Jake, um,
you know, it's incredible, incredible
job by Joe, uh, and John. Um
and yeah, he is, you know, such a
versatile player in our opinion. He's
just a real football player. Um
super excited to have him on our team.
>> So, uh initially competing at left
guard, you guys would say.
>> Yes.
>> And uh just watching the film, what did
you see that led you to believe that he
could be a fit at guard even though he
hadn't played there in the game? Again,
like I said, like you look at you and I
have had this conversation. We've had,
you know, talks throughout the year. You
look for plays where, okay, this is a
situation where he's got a man over his
hat, right? How's he handle that? How's
he anchor? Can he gain leverage? Can he
can he work the angle? And uh he does
all those things. And then you watch him
get up into space, watch him reach guys
at the second level, cut off backside
flow. He does all those things extremely
well. I think that's what we're going to
ask him to do at guard and center here.
So, uh, you know, he feel we feel like
he fits the bill for both positions.
>> He said that when he met with you guys
at the Senior Bowl in the combine, he
just had a good feeling. He felt he said
like feel like you guys saw eye to eye
and saw football the same way. Did you
both get that sense, too?
>> Yeah. Yeah, he had he I didn't meet with
him senior bowl, but he came into our
room in Indie and it was fun watching
him and coach like they were they were
locked in, you know, like the two of
them and uh great conversation and uh
just feel his presence, man. He's a man.
like he is a dude. Um and uh you know
just incredible intelligence. We've had
I've talked to other players at Florida
that literally
talked about how great of a leader and a
player he is and uh just he's an alpha
and uh and he's just he just you felt it
in the room. You walked out of there in
India and it was just like man, you
know, this would be a fun guy to take.
Yeah, it's incredible that we got uh
Tyler um in free agency and you know
Jake's been our top center uh for
uh through the entire process, top of
top of our board there with the ability
to play guard in our opinion at least uh
you know real good fighting chance to
compete even for the for the starting
position and we project that um at worst
if he's not starting at guard
then he'll be the next man in at all
three positions, guard, center, guard.
Um, so that's that's incredible value.
I, you know, predict u a couple years
from now that's going to be a highly
valuable uh value player and
uh another guy just uh you know, ball
player, willing to work, gonna come come
right in and and uh you know, just a
tremendous fit. I mean, at at a position
of of need. Um, also to have, you know,
young linemen under contract,
uh, that is, uh, that's huge. That's
that's something we needed.
>> How was Mike's reaction to the fake? You
saw him, even high five, just super
excited.
>> Yeah, he was he was excited.
>> Was he was he a guy he had kind of
championed throughout the process, too?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Our coaches are excited
about him. And uh again, it's a process
of of scouts and coaches and uh we want
to find players that we love, you know,
not not that individual scouts or
coaches love, you know, let's find the
ones that we all love together. And uh
he was one of those guys. He was a blue
star player for us, too. So, um
>> yeah,
>> your blue star player,
>> my he was my blue star.
>> He was a great pick, you know. Um
>> huh.
>> One of those.
>> Everyone, every scout gets one one blue.
Each scout gets one blue star.
>> It was mine.
>> That's why you came in.
>> No. No. I came in here because we got
all those picks and and we got a player
we liked, you know, like. So,
>> interior line, too.
>> Huh? They didn't? No. No. Uhuh. No. We,
you know, there was another there was
other players, you know, when we were
up, you know, that, you know, if he was
gone, we may not have been an offensive
lineman. So, I would had to come down
here and tell you there's plenty more of
offensive linemen that we like, you
know, and so, and that goes for multiple
positions. So, we're tomorrow's going to
be a fun day. I mean, I know the scouts
I when we traded back, I'm I looked at
all the scouts and they were excited
because they know what we do now. They
Chris is going to be in there, Mike's
going to be in there, Fix's going to be
in there, and all the coach and all the
scouts, and we're going to find the guys
that we really feel can help us win
games this year. the success that
>> the success that you've had on day three
these last two drafts target
>> day
Kamani sort of go down the list how much
confidence does that give you going into
tomorrow knowing that you know in your
two years you know you've had success in
this range of the draft
>> yeah I just I believe in the people in
the room that are helping make the
decisions and uh and that's the coaches
and the scouts and John and Jim and you
know my job is to organize it and uh and
and and
really make the decision on the pick,
listen to it. Certainly, I have a feel
for the players, too, but like it's us.
It's all of us. And uh and I love the
process and and I love the enthusiasm
everyone has with the process. So, I'm
excited to get up there. You know, I
know I had to come down here and talk to
you guys, but I can't wait to get back
up there. You know, it's just it's a
really fun process, and we're excited
about what we get to embark on tomorrow.
Are there positions like we asked you
before that you wouldn't take tomorrow?
They're pretty pretty wide open.
>> Yeah. Kicker and punter and long snapper
probably. So, um yeah,
>> pretty cool. We had five picks. Now we
got nine.
>> Yeah. So,
>> and um
>> but yeah, that's probably it.
>> What's tomorrow? Are you going to stay
all night or how do you rearrange?
>> No, the board's So, the board's already
set, right? the board's set and then we
just kind of we talk through them and
like and and all right, who do we who
who are the targets and the guy it's a
chance for the scouts to talk about the
players they really like and and really
want to go after tomorrow and uh and and
they've already they've gotten them up
to the spots they're in and the coaches
too and and Chris and Mike will talk
about their vision for each player and
and their their coach's vision and so it
you alls we really do is kind of spread
the board out a little bit. It's the the
order stays very similar, but it just it
it allows everyone to emphasize this
this is how this guy can help us and uh
paints a the clearest picture we can
have for tomorrow.
>> Have you ever had going back to
Baltimore, have you ever had seven picks
on the third day?
>> We we had six in the fourth round one
year. So, um which was a record which we
kept them all and that was that was a
that was a lot of picks in one round. I
mean, it just felt like we were on the
clock every every two minutes, you know?
So,
>> uh, that was
likely Isaiah likely. So, four year
Yeah. four I guess five drafts to go.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Isaiah Charlie was one of
them.
>> Um,
who else? Uh, Filet.
>> Oh, six played.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> At least five of the five of them were
contributors.
Was it as far as making these moves, was
it something specific about this draft
class where you, you know, wanted to
accumulate day three picks or is this
something you would have done like in
any year?
>> Uh, well, no. No, you got to look at the
board right as you're going and, you
know,
when we when we moved back in the
second, we had a stack of players and
it was, okay, if Jake's gone, would we
take this player? Yes. you know, okay,
so we we were able to move back. It just
so happened that Jake stayed, you know,
so we had a stack of guys that we felt
strongly about. If we move back, one of
these four guys will be there. And so we
did that. um this year, you know, in the
third round, you look at the board, it's
like, okay, like I told you, like there
there's going to be a lot of players
that they're all kind of in the same
range, same level. And uh let's just go
back and get some more picks because
there's still a lot of them up there
that we like and uh feel like we're
going to have a chance to get pick a lot
of them.
>> Do you do you want to make seven picks
tomorrow or are you viewing it as sort
of ammo to move up and be aggressive?
>> I think we're flexible on both ends. I
think we could, you know, move up. Heck,
we might move back and pick up a an
eighth pick. You never know um future
picks, you know. So, um I just it gives
you a
>> ton of flexibility, you know, firepower
to move up, firepower to gain picks for
next year, you know, so if a team's
interested. So,
>> even though you guys jad, you guys are
still willing to look at guard and and
other
>> the whole tackle everything. Yeah. You
know, we coach says it, you know,
competitors welcome. We want to make we
want to create the most competitive
environment we can out there and that's
the more players the better. Just uh
going back to Jake for a second, he got
some snaps at Garden Senior Bowl. How'd
you feel like he did?
>> We felt like that's that's one of the
things like, okay, yeah, he can do it.
He can develop and and continue to get
better at it and and get more
comfortable at it. But definitely felt
that showed his willingness,
flexibility. So, it's where we are with
that.
>> We didn't have a backup center.
>> Yeah, we Yeah. So yeah, I mean that's
the exciting thing about
>> the draft and and you you kind of final
you finalize your roster, you know, not
final final for the season, but now this
is our this is our team. And uh it's
great when you get a a player that's at
a need position and it's the top guy on
the board at that at that moment. That's
that's pretty great feeling, you know,
that's a that's a home run
type of scenario. So feel good about it.
Very very very excited. The other thing
too is like you know most all the time
you're uh you're looking at this as as a
guard and he could snap. You know you
know he took a couple snaps at the at
the senior bowl. I mean now you know you
got a center that can be a center.
There's no there's no projection there.
Probably the top center in the draft in
our opinion. Uh but he can also also
play guard. That's that's uh it doesn't
usually happen that
>> that fortunately.
>> I think that's the cool thing about the
Senior Bowl.
>> Fits us.
>> Yeah, I think that's the cool thing
about Senior Bowl. They they've been
doing it for a long time now. They can
just they take like coach said, they
take guards, they put them tackles, they
put them at guards, they put tackles,
put them at center. You just that's, you
know, gets see guys in multiple
positions. So, um, you see inside
backers playing on the edge like, you
know, it's All-Star games are great just
to and you really you just watch them do
drills, you know, they're all their hand
they may not have the ball in in drills,
you know, and just they got their hand
in the ground and how they look, how
they move, you know. So,
>> yeah, he's it' be it'll be it'll be I
think it'd be cool when he's here when
he gets he's coming tomorrow. See?
>> No, no, we should get him here. I'd like
to see him on the hood, you know,
because it's gonna I mean, he's gonna
look he's gonna look he good, you know,
he's 64 and a half and some change, you
know, and uh you know, it's good that
fits in there with uh with the rest of
our line and and uh you know, tall
quarterback.
Take the big guys.
>> Right now in late April, how are you
liking the way your of mind is kind of
running out with obviously Joe and
everybody coming back and some of the
additions that you guys have made.
>> Uh like I said yesterday, I mean, I
think we're uh we're in a tremendous
place. Uh
our are in our entire roster uh that is
in is in a in a place physically that's
that's really good. uh every every
single guy and um you know it's when you
get those kind of guys you know you get
the right kind of guys uh you know
gritty tough guys that want to work who
are really talented who give talent and
effort and you get the right coaches uh
together and then you you bring in the
right uh you have the right kind of
draft uh and that that keeps building
and and working and then you look down
and go Okay, there's a ring. You know,
there's another one. That uh that's the
way it feels.
>> Uh how do you feel about Jake's anchor
in pass protection?
>> Good. Good.
>> Yeah. Strong, square,
athletic.
>> Um and then just it feels like you got
the edge in round one, you know,
competitive piece of the left guard.
Felt like two of your bigger needs, you
know, coming into the draft. Was the
plan always to address these two
positions in some capacity in the first
two days? And I mean, how does it feel
to
>> feels good to have done it? It feels It
does feel good to have have done it. Um
I think the plan going into the draft is
>> Yeah, we have areas where we can add
more depth and uh uh or where we may
need a little bit more depth than
others. And uh but you don't you don't
do it for the sake of doing it. You do
it when when it's right, when the time's
right. And um it just matched up, you
know. Uh yesterday was easy. Today was
easy. You know, just you know that's the
when you when a a need matches the best
player available, it it really is easy,
you know. And uh I know there's some
years where I've only been here for two
and a half drafts. Coach and I have only
been here for two and a half drafts, but
I remember a time when we took a guy
that people didn't perceive as a need
and uh he's been all right, you know.
So, you know, I I I like him, you know,
and he's done pretty good. So, um, you
know, you just you just take the best
players and sometimes it matches a need,
sometimes it doesn't, you know, but in
the long run, in the end, four years
from now, when that player's playing for
you, you're like, damn, I'm glad I
picked him, you know, glad we picked
him, you know, cuz we didn't we didn't
we didn't force a guy off the board
because of need. We took the best player
and this is what you get.
>> It's only second day. We're just we're
still right in it. So,
>> yeah. No deep long vows. Just still
still just grinding. That's that's what
we're doing.
>> I don't know either.
>> Chargers or Ravens? The Chargers. Okay.
>> Joe. Joe.
>> I mean, well, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I don't
know. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Perceived need. I should say
perceived need
>> by who?
>> People
reporters.
>> No, it's the draft is the draft, man.
You just you got to stick to what you
believe in and your process. And that's
what we do. And uh we have we set our
board. We take the best players, you
know, and again, that's what I tell you.
When the when you got two guys that are
even, then you let need play in. But you
never let need dictate position, you
know, move a guy up because then you
reach on a guy
and then you watch the other guy three
years from now like, damn, we should
have took him. you know, but